a. What is the definition of a “signed number”?
A signed number has bit that usually precedes the binary integer, to denote whether it is negative or positive number.

b. What is the definition of an “unsigned number”?
An unsigned number does not have this sign bit to denote whether its positive or negative, so an unsigned integer can be a higher value in the same amount of bits, but only in the positive direction.

c. Give an example of how to write a negative number in binary.
You could have 1 1001, to denote a -9, or a 0 1001 to denote a 9.

d. In programming, what is a “flag”?
A flag is an arbitrarily assigned variable, that is supposed to denote something. In dealing with negative numbers in binary, a flag would be the sign bit assigned to the number to denote whether a number is positive or negative.

e. What is “numeric overflow”?
In computers, the amount that can be represented in a number is constrained by how many bits can be processed, and if a value were created that exceeded that number of bits, an error would occur and it wouldn't be represented correctly. For example, if we had a 4-bit computer, in binary the maximum value represented in 4 binary places is 1111 or 15, because to represent any higher in binary would be 10000 but that would take 5 bits instead of 4.

f. Write the following fractional numbers in binary:
1 ½ = 1.1
22 ¾ = 10110.11
113 ⅓ = 01110001.010101010101...